They always say that
"At Google, you're working with
a lot of the best and the brightest."
I think that is true.
My name is, Kourtni Marshall.
I'm an application engineer
at Corp Eng in Google.
Corp Eng is basically the IT of Google.
And our main mission
is to keep Google productive internally.
We create applications
mainly for my fellow Googlers
that solve everyday
problems that we might have.
The thing that I love
about being an engineer
is figuring out how to
solve these problems,
like, there's a problem that we have.
And, right now, it's going unanswered.
But, with the work that
myself and others do,
we can make that problem go away.
My father had dropped out of high school.
My brother had dropped out of high school,
and I was on the path of like,
eh, maybe I'll drop out of high school.
The only reason I'm even here
is because a friend of mine
in high school literally saw
me checking out a little bit,
and said, "Hey, here's some resources
to get you back on track."
So, I have to recognize
that without people looking out for me,
I probably wouldn't be where I'm at today.
And I was also blessed because my father,
he ended up getting us a old computer.
But, we were like one of the
only people on the block
that had a computer in their house.
I was seven years old, and
I remember the first thing
I really learned on it was
a language called Basic.
And, all I could figure out how to do,
I'd read the things,
I could figure out how to
make what was called a Sprite,
move across the screen.
And I was like, wow, this is awesome!
So, I think that's one of the
things that actually moved me
toward being interested
in computers at all.
To be successful at Google,
you have to have a drive to learn.
There's so many things to learn
within the company itself.
And there's so many opportunities, really,
to have an impact within the company.
Especially if you have that
desire to find those things
that you really are most passionate about,
and then kinda do deep
dives into those things.